# Azm Mohibul Haque Surov

2014 to 2022 - 8 years is a long time but in the end, whether you go forward or backward is decided by what you do every single day. Nothing is achieved for free unless you're God-gifted like Lionel Messi. But I was born a very average guy and that's why I've always followed Cristiano Ronaldo's motto of working hard. For the past 8 years, I have worked in different industries with different roles but during this period, I got accustomed to a fast-paced environment where time deadlines are a priority and handling multiple jobs simultaneously is a requirement. I enjoy this challenge and work hard to attain my goals.



azm.surov@gmail.com



www.azms.me



in linkedin.com/in/azms



github.com/AzmSurov

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Product Specialist Bold Commerce**

08/2020 - Present

Winnipeg, MB

Bold Commerce is a software development company that provides industry-leading eCommerce solutions for the world's most innovative brands.

- Integrated web applications for Shopify and Woocommerce customer
- Implemented fixes to the front-end of e-commerce websites using HTML, CSS and **Javascript**
- Collaborated with other team members and stakeholders to develop new user-facing features
- Responded to Merchant queries about products and bug reports using Zendesk and Jira
- Ensured the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs
- Assured all user input was validated before submitting to back-end

### **Operations Specialist**

SkipTheDishes

12/2019 - 02/2021

Winnipeg, MB

Apply Skip's technology and tools to continuously optimize the efficiency of the network.

- Apply Skips in-house software technology and tools to multitask in continuously identifying problems and optimizing the efficiency of the network leading to greater customer satisfaction.
- Resolve problems or potential breaches within the network to ensure a steady flow
- Pro-actively manage the network's performance from making important logistical decisions to ensuring each stakeholder's experience meets Skip's experience standards.

### **Logistics Controller**

SkipTheDishes

09/2017 - 12/2018 Control Team 1

Winnipeg, MB

- Provide live support to couriers, customers, and restaurants.
- Resolving conflicts with an emphasis on helping our partners succeed.
- Communicate between all parties involved in each delivery.

Teamwork

Leadership

Strong Communication

**Problem Solving** 

Time Management

Empathy

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

### **Proficient**

JavaScript • React • Next.js • Context API • RESTFul API • HTML5 • CSS3 • SCSS • MongoDB • MySQL • Git • Redux • Firebase • GraphQL

#### **Familiar**

Jest • Cypress • Jasmine

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

### Link Shortner

- This is a React and Firebase App which generates shortened links. You can create and save as many links you want and share it others. The app is similar other sites like bitly.com or tinyurl.com
- View it live at https://shortly-44afc.web.app/

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

### Employee of the Month (03/2018)

I was awarded employee of the month at SkipTheDishes for having the highest number of actions solved.

## **EDUCATION**

### **Bachelor of Arts - Economics** University Of Manitoba

01/2014 - 08/2020

Minor

Computer Science



Winnipeg, MB